(Production Sponsors)
(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism and KOCCA)
(This is a work of fiction. All names, characters, )
(and incidents are products of the author's imagination.)
(All child actors were accompanied by a guardian, )
(and filmed in accordance with labour laws.)
(Python Hacking Programming)
(10am, Creative Integrated Design)
To think I woke up on time even after that whole ordeal...
means any drama with a guy doesn't affect me anymore.
After going through enough trial and error,
I have a simple, efficient system for any romantic entanglements.
All these past embarrassments are now just useful data.
Right now, I'm completely in control.
(Memory Motel)
(Daejeon)
I'm surprised they have an automated motel out here.
Hey, that's Kang Min Hak.
He's a really nice guy.
Gosh, darn it!
- Maybe it's not automated. - Should we go somewhere else?
I'll get out of your way.
I'll be gone in a second.
- Oh, we can just go. - Just a minute!
Just because it's an automated motel doesn't mean no one's here.
What if a toilet gets clogged? I have to be here to unclog it.
And guests at your age go through 4 or 5 condoms a night, you know?
If they need more, I run them up.
We're on call for things like that, watching you on the cameras.
- Cameras? - What?
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Hold on. Wait a second!
Good grief, what are you saying?
No, not hidden cameras. He means the ones here in the lobby.
Gosh, we'd never use hidden cameras.
I have a kid your age.
We're actually the cleanest motel in the area.
- We're even Clean Tag certified. - We did.
I bet we're the only place around that disinfects it all with alcohol.
This is creepy.
Creepy? What's so creepy about it?
The security camera is over there.
See? Right there.
- Right here. - Let's just go.
Well...
(CCTV recording in progress)
You and your big mouth.
They looked to be San's age.
I wonder if our daughter will start using automated motels.
Why would a motel owner's daughter do that?
She even went to high school with a dormitory to escape motels.
Maybe we should get a kiosk.
They say it does one person's job.
Where would we get the money?
They're three thousand dollars, even used!
We spent all our extra cash getting a top ad spot on this booking app.
The model on our booking app has a lovely smile, don't you think?
I like him smiling.
What's so great about it?
Bills are high, we have no business, and we're about to go under.
(LOVE.exe)
(Episode 6: Not That Kind of M.T.)
So we're a team now?
Hope we get along well.
Same here. This is the most exciting project!
So what made you change your mind?
Was it really because San asked you to join?
Well...
Ji No was a bit much for me.
He was live-posting how many times I used the bathroom on social media.
And...
- a teammate confessed she liked me. - A teammate? Who?
Them two? The ex-Treasurer's girlfriend?
So you made a couple break up.
They started fighting and crying, and it was awkward in the middle.
Anyway, the whole thing was a mess.
But you all seemed completely uninterested in me.
- What? - Like, whether I'm handsome or not,
popular or not,
none of that seemed to matter.
You seemed to only want to focus on the work.
Anyway, I'm a lot more comfortable with you guys.
If so, you made a great choice.
- Right, Na Rae? - Sure.
No one's going to confess to Min Hak...
and make things hard for him, right?
- Not me, at least. - Never?
I wouldn't say never.
- What? - What?
Maybe three percent?
What?
That's the probability of one of us...
falling for you, Kang Min Hak.
- That's what my stats say. - Three percent?
Is that high?
Wait, what data are you using?
If the Apocalypse hits, you must help preserve the species.
Are you working on the premise of human extinction or something?
I'm surprised you feel responsible for future generations, San.
So when it's not the end of the world,
would I have zero chance of being a couple with Min Hak?
Wait, can you guys just do that math in your head on the fly?
You guys are really something else.
I know I'm not quite on your level,
but I promise I'll do my absolute best.
Let's do this!
- Let's do this! - Let's do this!
He just drew a line, right? "Don't you dare fall for me."
Yes.
Kang Min Hak's a real pro. Doesn't he know that's attractive?
- Lucky! - Nice.
Lucky.
- Hello? - Joo Yeon San, where are you now?
- At school. - What floor are we on?
- Why? What's up? - First floor?
- Dad has a quick trip to Seoul. - For example,
- I told you about this before. - when you’re told not to think...
- about an elephant, - Remember?
- that’s all you can think about. - Hello?
Did the call drop?
Conversely, what if Min Hak says, "I hope you fall for me?"
She'd probably just go, "Okay, I will."
Na Rae, we need to get paid.
Let's not scare Kang Min Hak off, all right?
I should add Min Hak to our group chat, right?
- Min Hak, welcome to the team. - Howdy.
Howdy to you too.
I have a group meeting in 2 days at 3.
What?
Hey, I told you to just freeload.
Why waste gas money coming here?
What if they only want to hit on you?
Be careful.
No way. With them, there's absolutely no...
Well, I wouldn't say never.
The probability is just extremely low.
Maybe a three percent chance?
That's according to my data.
Three percent? Get real.
We don't have time for that.
There was an article saying...
Jinny's soju commercial contract was up.
Apparently, Amy is the next model. That's how this industry is.
One is pushed out, another comes in. Min Hak, you must be the next one.
- Wait, this is 60 dollars? - Yes.
The department jacket is 60 dollars?
They should be cheap to wear out.
Lots of pockets, comfy as a pillow, and stain-resistant. That’s all.
Right, because CompSci's design was a pillow with a fishing vest.
That was a great idea for storing your essentials in separate pockets.
Except that option got almost no votes.
That includes the logo design fee, and the Tatami embroidery is pricey.
But it's black-on-black embroidery. You can't even see it.
No one will see this as a department jacket.
That's the whole point.
If we don't hit the minimum order, the price goes up even more.
Come on. You think we won't?
Hey, everyone, wait up! Come here and try this on.
Is that the jacket?
- Hold on. - Is that the jacket?
- Hold on. - This is way too big.
Hold on. Hey, stop pushing.
Excuse me! I need to get out.
Excuse me! We're packed in too tight.
One idea from each of you by the day after tomorrow.
(One idea from each of you by the day after tomorrow)
Of course, this isn't a competition for the best proposal or anything.
Got it!
(Kang Min Hak: Got it!)
- You're here. - Goodness!
Dad!
Some dried anchovies and shredded squid.
And this is seasoned deodeok root, your favourite.
I didn't know you were coming.
Would tomorrow be any different?
And a hydrating, nourishing ampoule.
Kills two birds with one stone.
Mom sent this for your dry skin.
Here, use it.
Hey, what's this?
This is a classic from my day.
Is this the Gen Z vibe now?
Gosh, do you even cook for yourself?
What's all this? Clean this up.
You just let it pile up. When is recycling day?
Don't throw that away. I'm saving it to sell.
I get more money for a full box.
Gosh, the dildo!
Dad! I'll clean this up.
- No, I'll do it. - Really, I've got it.
Since I'm here, I'll just clean the whole place.
Well, actually,
the caulking under the toilet needs to be redone.
- The caulking? - Yes.
I'll work on it after this.
- No, don't. - Why are you pushing me?
- Please go check on it now. - Why are you pushing me?
It looks perfectly fine to me.
It doesn't even wobble when I sit on it.
There's nothing wrong with it.
No, it's a huge problem.
Did you actually sit down?
I'm telling you, it rattles and shakes when you sit down.
- Really? - Just caulk it anyway.
The real problem is the mold.
Are you cleaning out the cabinets now?
Leave it. I'll take care of all that for you tomorrow.
No, it's okay. You don't have to do this part.
There's some personal girl stuff in there.
- Is that right? - Yes.
So you keep that kind of stuff in the kitchen?
So, Dad, why did you say you were in town again?
Oh, right. I have a wedding to go to this weekend.
So you're staying here until then?
Yes. It's not for business.
I wanted a change of scenery and to meet up with some friends.
I don't need you to co-sign anything!
All right.
Then I'll just stay out of your hair.
But just this one thing.
Why is he popping up there?
This model guy.
Doesn't he go to your school?
Could you get me his autograph?
You're not asking me to get it, are you?
Yes, and tell him I'm a huge fan.
When I'm down, seeing him smile...
just makes me smile too.
And tell him to keep looking good.
What are you even talking about?
Why not? If our motel has a star's autograph,
think how great that would be.
It builds credibility.
Here.
(Number one in Customer Satisfaction)
(Today, right now...)
(penguintan0129)
Should I follow him first?
(penguintan0129 started following you)
Na Rae, are you home?
(Gil Tan: Na Rae, are you home?)
Yes. What's up?
Perfect. I just need a roll of toilet paper.
I'll give you two back tomorrow.
Just toss it out the window.
What the?
Okay.
Catch.
Throw it.
Thank you.
Seriously? He followed me just to ask for toilet paper?
(SUPER LIKE! Swipe to find out who)
(Memory Motel)
Did Dad go out?
(Hangang University)
We're set for the hotel staycation vlog tomorrow.
- Where? - Right across the street.
Don't tell me it's one of those motels over there.
It's a franchise,
and I didn't see the point in going far to film.
I asked the branch near the school to make it easy for you.
I don't mind travelling.
I do. It's a pain for me.
You can just walk there and back.
I'm kidding. They remodelled anyway, so it looks good.
Where could Dad have gone so early?
Is that Kang Min Hak?
What was that? Did I just wave at Kang Min Hak?
- It was the client's request. - Let me out here.
Why? What's wrong?
Why? Hey...
See you later.
What's going on?
Close the door!
San! Joo Yeon San!
- Hi. - Hi.
How did you know it was me?
It's hard to see inside.
I'd know that mint car anywhere.
I have a favour to ask. It's fine if you won't do it.
From me?
- Right. - What is it?
Well, my dad runs a motel.
And it turns out you're the model for the booking app he uses.
He's a big fan and asked if I could get your autograph.
An autograph?
This brings back memories of when we first met.
- If you're making a dumb joke... - What's his name?
- Sorry? - Your father's name.
Right.
Joo Jong Hwan.
- Jong Hwan? - Yes.
- San. - Yes?
Can you turn around for a second?
- I need to use your back. - My back?
- Just for this. Yes. - Okay.
Hold on.
(Right Here)
By the way,
did you come all the way to campus just for this?
Of course not. I had no idea when you'd be here.
Right.
There we go.
Thanks. I didn't misspell it this time.
Right, though that wasn't why you misspelled it last time.
Hey, you.
Is this how you act in meetings, too?
Hey.
You can't keep coming on to him.
Don't misuse his kindness.
I wanted to do it, so I asked her for it.
How is this crossing a line? This is just being nice to a fan.
- You waste time on useless stuff... - If it wasn't for my dad...
You grant every trivial favour asked.
Do you know how frustrating that is?
That's right. My dad's a lot, so I asked a favour.
I won't bother you again, so you should watch your words too.
So I don't waste more of your time, I'll be on my way.
Hey...
Why didn't you just keep driving if you were just going to clam up?
Come on.
She's really something else.
(To Joo Jong Hwan, Thank you, Kang Min Hak)
At least this will keep Dad off my back.
Okay, I'm leaving. Right away.
What?
Oh, dear.
- What's going on? - You can just take that one, then.
- Does this one go there? - Yes.
Okay. Perfect.
You've gone to so much trouble for me today.
Why is Dad at a motel with another woman?
Of all potential family problems, an affair was...
something I thought had less than a three percent chance of happening.
You said it was a little loose, so I fixed it.
I'm almost done.
Just be careful not to get it wet for about three days.
So, where were you today?
Me? I went to Seoul to meet up with a friend.
Since the crack of dawn?
Getting older makes time precious.
I'm just going to step out for a bit.
Where'd my socks go?
Am I jumping to conclusions? Or am I just slow to see the truth?
Something feels off.
- "Want to meet up later?" - Hey, why are you reading that?
Your Tinder match? Hey, let me see his picture.
Let's see if he's a good one this time.
"This time?" I've barely used it. You're being so extra.
- You said he was a hot guy. - When did I say "hot guy?"
I was just doing market research, checking out the dating app scene.
How can you trust someone enough to meet them from an app?
Seriously? We're developing an app right now.
Let's not hate on apps.
If there are problems with these kinds of apps,
we need to think about what solutions we can provide.
Minimize the risks,
and have an eye for enhancing the positive functions and benefits.
Having an eye for those things...
is how you come up with good ideas.
So, did you come up with a good idea?
Of course I did.
I've been thinking,
since it's people our age voting on this anyway,
we definitely have to do something related to dating.
"Does he like me?"
"Or who does she like?"
"Who gives me the biggest hit of dopamine?"
That's all that matters for those in their 20s.
Not for me.
Sure, some people are like you, but we want mass appeal, right?
Why else would a show set in some shabby-looking guesthouse...
with a regular guys and girls, like on "I Am Solo,"
be more popular than a huge drama with A-list stars?
So you're saying we should launch something kind of like Tinder?
No way. We have to approach it differently.
Something cute that only we can pull off.
For example, an alarm that goes off if someone you like is within 10m,
something like the "Love Alarm."
The fact that it's been adapted into a webtoon and a drama...
shows what the public desires.
But is it even possible to actually make that?
It's appeared on TV shows, but commercializing it will be hard.
Even if it's not the "Love Alarm,"
we can make an app to help with love.
Recommending nice places for anniversaries,
showing available discounts, and suggesting places like hotels.
How often do students really go to hotels?
Maybe not hotels, but trust me, they go to motels all the time.
For example, going on a hotel staycation with friends?
Should we do that sometime?
Right. A "Right Here" hotel opened up front.
The hotel that opened up out front?
Where? In the middle of all these motels?
Yes. I'm here to film a vlog today.
I heard it was newly renovated.
Should I send some gift certificates for the chain?
Gift certificates? Yes, please.
It's just that I'm an ambassador for this app.
Please. They just renovated a motel and slapped "hotel" on the sign.
Seriously? Right in front of the ambassador?
That word always cracks me up.
Why does everyone call commercial models...
"ambassadors" these days?
Hey, there must be some difference.
Anyway, that's great, Min Hak.
Let us know how it is once you've been.
I don't get why people go to motels when they have their own homes.
A house isn't always the most private place.
Motels are so bad for the environment.
What's with the friendly fire? Your family runs a motel, you know.
That's how I know.
The amount of disposables is insane.
Toothbrushes, toothpaste, cotton swabs,
and even used condoms.
You know what the trash looks like?
It's like the building took a dump.
Not to mention...
They're also breeding grounds for affairs.
Yeon San.
Why would you call your family's business a dump?
Right.
San, I get your concern,
but motels partnered with "Right Here..."
are supposedly run in a very eco-friendly way.
They use bamboo toothbrushes,
and you can even opt out of receiving amenities.
I wasn't talking about you.
I know. But still, I'm their ambassador.
The "ambassador."
You know I care for the environment.
So when I sign an endorsement deal,
I always make sure the company is eco-friendly.
And I recently...
became a golf course ambassador.
- A golf course? - And they're even partnered...
with a recycled apparel company.
How is a golf course eco-friendly?
San, you've never been to one, have you?
They're incredibly eco-friendly.
- Okay, let's get back on topic. - Right.
Especially the golf club I promote, the "Stay Green Golf Course,"
has such beautiful natural surroundings.
Birds are chirping all over,
and you can see fish swimming in the lake.
I'll give you some guest passes, so you should come sometime...
They build golf courses by literally carving up mountains.
Carving up mountains?
But there are tons of trees there.
The trees were moved from elsewhere, and the fish were just put there.
The grass is perfectly manicured. It's so lush and green.
Do you know how much pesticide they use to keep that grass green?
What about the major water shortages that municipalities face every year?
And yet they waste tons of water on golf courses to keep them green?
What does that have to do with anything?
He can learn now. He's all heart, not brains. Right?
"Not brains?"
- "Brains." - Kang Min Hak,
I see environment care is...
- just an accessory for you. - An accessory?
Why would you call it an accessory?
I'm being serious.
Okay.
If you're being genuine,
then you're a perfect case study...
of how people unintentionally ruin the world.
So you're saying I'm destroying the world?
When you're that ignorant, instead of trying to be responsible,
it's better to just stay quiet.
Especially for someone like you, who clearly influences others,
being ignorant is being irresponsible!
San.
Hey!
(I'm an alum. Can I still buy a department jacket?)
(Dong Won, I'm one of Jae Seon's seniors.)
(I heard the department jackets are sold out.)
Dong Won, planning another round of department jacket orders?
(Department Jacket World)
What is going on?
Hey, Hold on!
I keep getting calls for department jackets,
even from the alumni.
Look at this.
We got so many requests to buy one, so we made an Outsider Edition.
Just from this morning's pre-orders, we've already sold over 300.
What? Who'd buy other school's jacket?
- We just passed 400. - What?
The Outsider Edition is profitable.
I marked up the price a little.
- Which means... - We've hit the jackpot.
We got that sponsored skincare, so put some on after you wash up.
It has the eco ingredients you like.
So give it a shout-out on camera.
(Eco-friendly golf course)
This is just a simple product placement.
Hey, are you even listening to me?
This is a field I might know more about than you.
Skincare?
Right. Of course you'd know more.
But still, for the business side, you promised you'd trust me on this.
I just went with a brand that was easy to negotiate with.
(Eco-friendly golf course)
Not much is coming up on Naver.
Okay, I'll get your opinion first from now on.
Golf course.
Eco-friendly golf course.
(Golf course. Eco-friendly golf course)
Eco...
- A golf course? - Eco...
So you're itching to get out on the green?
Okay, I'll book a tee time right now.
(So you're itching to get out...)
But for today's vlog, at least, we must plug this Schwanengarten.
Hey!
Sorry, just be quiet for a minute.
Please.
(But for today's vlog, at least, we must plug this Schwanengarten.)
The search isn't working.
Eco-friendly golf course.
I got way too worked up because of my dad.
I ended up projecting my issues onto an innocent Kang Min Hak.
I need to reflect on how I was being logical, yet illogical.
Same thing here.
Ignoring a problem you know exists only makes it worse.
Instead of nectar from flowers, bees are intoxicated by pesticides.
They were wiped out in massive numbers.
The cause is a neighbouring golf course.
They had drenched the greens in pesticides the day before.
Mother bees, father bees, baby bees...
So she was right all along.
She was right about everything.
There's no such thing as an "eco-friendly" golf course.
I'm so sorry, little bees.
And the rabbits,
the deer too.
I'm sorry to all of you.
For a stupid ball game, I...
No, not me, but...
We destroyed all your homes.
We humans are sorry.
Mom.
(Ward A)
Thank you for always calling me Mom so freely.
But you are my mom.
No matter what, you'll always be my mom.
Min Hak, you take after your father.
With that handsome face of yours,
it'll be very easy for you to win people's hearts.
But what's important...
isn't that brief moment when you win someone's heart,
it's holding onto that heart responsibly for the long haul.
When you make a mistake or do something wrong,
you have to own up to it and apologise right away.
That's what a good person does.
Your father and I couldn't do that,
but you should be a good person, Min Hak.
Make sure you listen to your grandfather, okay?
Ma'am, when you go to Australia, be wary of the Korean community.
The people who prey on Koreans overseas the most...
are other Koreans.
All right. Thank you for looking out for me.
Take care, Jae Hak.
(Ward A)
Mom. Don't go.
Mom.
This is all because your father lived like a playboy.
I should know.
I once lived off these dashing good looks myself.
But it's just a fleeting shortcut to total ruin.
It takes more than a pretty face to be a real man.
Min Hak.
Mark my words.
You heard what that woman said?
Just because the ladies like you, don't let it go to your head...
and blame the world for everything.
If you keep blaming everyone else, you'll end up just like your father.
A pretty flower that's quick to wilt.
A playboy.
That's exactly who I was.
Irresponsible,
a pretty boy who was nothing more than a flower.
Just like an eco-friendly golf course.
They say, "The first flower to bloom is the first to wilt."
Because of global warming, cherry blossoms are blooming early.
Maybe my hair loss, too.
Schwanengarten sent me some of their cosmetics to try,
so I've been using them, and I absolutely love them.
(So handsome in the ad! Going to watch it again)
I think this is going to be my new go-to.
(Your skin is perfect.)
I love that it keeps my skin hydrated all day long,
and everything from the ingredients to the packaging is eco-friendly.
(That face is magic. Did Hogwarts send an owl?)
(Seriously, don't you dare work out. You're already too perfect.)
(Is something wrong? Your expression suddenly changed.)
(You seem down today. Are you okay?)
(You're not sick, are you? I'm worried)
(What's wrong?)
(I'm worried. You don't seem like yourself.)
(I missed the start of the stream. Did something happen?)
(Just got here. What's with the vibe?)
(Who gets depressed while putting on lotion?)
Eco-friendly...
(Safety first)
(Smooth Taste, Like Dew)
(No.1 Soju, made with spring water)
Jinny.
When will I finally be a responsible adult?
Someone who pulls their own weight?
Man, I'm so horny today.
- Let's go. - I really need to get laid.
- Let's do it. I'll make a call. - I want to do it.
- No way. - Seriously.
Look, Jinny's passed out.
I should help our girl Jinny up.
Hey, knock her over, you idiot.
When else do we get her on her back?
Hey.
Who says you have to do it lying down, you punk?
- You can do it standing up too. - This punk's an animal when drunk.
That fool.
- Hey, stop it. - Why can't anyone just grow up?
- Stop it, that's disgusting. - Dude, you're going too far.
Hey, people are watching! I said stop!
- Hey, you're acting crazy. - Here, let me try.
Stop it, there are people around.
- Just stop it! - Hey!
What do you want?
(Smooth Taste, Like Dew)
Darn it.
Come on.
- What the... - Is that guy a pervert or what?
- Sir, that guy took it! - That pervert, that's him!
- Get him! He's a pervert. - Stop, thief!
I should just get out of here.
I need to pull my own weight.
I will pull my weight right now.
It's time to be an adult.
I'm so sorry.
Kang Min Hak?
San? What are you doing here?
Miss! Stop that guy. He's a pervert!
- What's going on? - Get back here, you pervert!